Guide to the IBT Magazine Advertisement Ephemera, 1919-1962 IBT0088
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
IBT Magazine Advertisement Ephemera Collection
1919-1962
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
International Brotherhood of Teamsters
IBT0088
1.5 document boxes 1 flat oversize document box containing advertisements from the Saturday Evening Post re truck and trucking
Conditions Governing Access
This collection is open for research.
Arrangement
Series in this collection are organized alphabetically.
Scope and Contents
This collection is comprised of one series of magazine advertisements for trucking companies affiliated with the International Brotherhood of Teamsters. The collection ranges from 1919-1962.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters
Advertising, Magazine; Trucking -- United States; International Brotherhood of Teamsters
- Trucking Advertisements, 1919-1962; Series 1; 1.5 Linear Feet One over-sized flat box
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains magazine advertisements of trucking companies and other topics pretaining to the trucking industry. Companies including in this series are Ford, Hertz, The White Motor Company, and Four Wheel Drive Auto Company.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically by title.
  - American Trucking Industry "Where's your job when war ends?" advertisement, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - ATA Foundation Ford Division, Inc Safety Check advertisement, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - A.T.A. Truck Roadeo National Championships Advertisement, Saturday Evening Post, Chicago, Illinois, September 26, 1946; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ford Trucks Last Longer! Advertisement, 1948; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Four Wheel Drive Auto Company Trucks Advertisement, The Saturday Evening Post, May 31, 1919; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Hertz Truck Rental System Advertisement, Chicago, Illinois, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - International Harvester Company "Safety's Roving Ambassador" advertisement, Washington, DC, 1962; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - International Harvester Company Trucks Avertisement, The Saturday Evening Post, Chicago, Illinois, October 20, 1951; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - International Truck A.T.A. Truck Roadeo National Championships Advertisement, 1946; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - The White Motor Company "America's Secret Weapon", Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - The White Motor Company "Miles by the Millions", The Saturday Evening Post, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - The White Motor Company "The Land of Plenty Needs Plenty of This" Advertisement, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - The White Motor Company "Trucks that Come to Dinner" advertisement, Undated; Series 1 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Time Magazine with Teamster Ad, 1974 September 2; IBT 0088 Series 1 (Box Shared Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Time Magazine with Teamster Ad, 1974 September 2; IBT 0088 Series 1 (Box Shared Box 30, Folder 1)